A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 3, Accession 3 FA1185
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Exchanges from China, 1976-1978, 1980; 4
  - FA1185:036 - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Media Luncheon (New York), 1977 July 7; Audio Cassette tape (120 minutes) (Box FA1185:036, Folder 252)
    Presentation on Role of the Media in Foreign Affairs.
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Visits (Chicago), 1977 June 27-July 19 (Box 29, Folder 253)
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Visits (Des Moines, IA), 1977 June 27-July 19 (Box 29, Folder 254)
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Visits (Berkeley, San Francisco, Stanford), 1977 June 27-July 19 (Box 29, Folder 255)
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Visits (Los Angeles), 1977 June 27-July 19 (Box 29, Folder 256)
  - FA1185:024 - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Visits (Los Angeles), 1977 June 27-July 19; Still Image: 3x5 color snapshot (Box 34, Folder 256)
    Image of Governor Brown and Mayor Bradley with delegation, circa July 18, 1978. File also makes reference to photo albums from the delegation's visit to the Rand Corporation, but no copies have been identified.
  - Chinese People's Institute of Foreign Affairs Delegation: Thank Yous, 1977 June 27-July 19 (Box 29, Folder 257)
  - Soccer Team Visit: General, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 29, Folder 258)
    Itinerary, rosters, contacts, guidelines.
  - Soccer Team Visit: Background and Planning, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 29, Folder 259)
  - Soccer Team Visit: Brochure, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 29, Folder 260)
  - Soccer Team Visit: Budget and Accounting, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 29, Folder 261)
    Includes correspondence with Patrick Nally (West Nally Group) and Gene Edwards (United States Soccer Federation).
  - Soccer Team Visit: Visits and Matches, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 30, Folder 262 - 263)
  - Soccer Team Visit: Miami Incident, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 30, Folder 264)
  - Soccer Team Visit: Press Coverage, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 30, Folder 265)
  - FA1185:029 - Soccer Team Visit: Press Coverage, 1977 October 3-18; Oversized: Newspapers (Box FA1185:029, Folder 265)
    China Daily News, volume 38, no. 58 (1977 September 28); no. 64 (1977 October 8); nos. 65-67 (1977 October 10 - 12); nos. 69-71 (1977 October 15 - 18).
  - FA1185:025 - Soccer Team Visit: Press Coverage, 1977 October 3-18; Still Image: 2 black and white 8x10 glossy prints. (Box 34, Folder 265)
    Two promotional images of unidentified soccer teams entering on playing field.
  - Soccer Team Visit: Thank Yous and Follow-Up, 1977 October 3-18 (Box 30, Folder 266)
  - Higher Education Delegation: General, 1977 November 19-December 17 (Box 30, Folder 268)
    Namelists, guidelines, budget, guest lists; Thank Yous and Follow-Up
  - Higher Education Delegation: Visits and Meetings, 1977 November 19-December 17 (Box 30, Folder 269)
  - Higher Education Delegation: Report, 1977 November 19-December 17 (Box 30, Folder 270)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: General, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 30, Folder 271)
    Itineraries, Guidelines and Contacts, Information on Chinese Teams
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Background and Planning (1 of 2), 1978 November 8-19 (Box 30, Folder 272)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Background and Planning (2 of 2), 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 273)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Jay Henderson Working File, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 274)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Contract, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 275)
    Promotion Agreement with Madison Square Garden. Includes some financial reporting.
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: PepsiCo - Wilson Sponsorship, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 276)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Press Coverage, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 277)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Program Booklet, Basketball Rules, and Game Scores, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 278)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Visits and Games, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 279)
    Includes City Profiles (in Chinese).
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Scrapbook and Team Photos, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 280)
    Scrapbook consists of loose pages of clippings, tickets, and photocopied snapshots.
  - FA1185:026 - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Scrapbook and Team Photos, 1978 November 8-19; Still Images: Black and white 5"x6" prints and duplicates, plus copy negative of each photo. (Box 34, Folder 280)
    Group photos of men's and women's teams (2 images - 7 prints of each, plus 1 of each print retained in document file).
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Teams: Thank Yous, 1978 November 8-19 (Box 31, Folder 281)
- Publications and Reports, 1971-2014; 6
  The Publications and Reports series in RG 3 contains the National Committee's China Policy Series pamphlets, numbers 1 – 23 (1989 – 2007), as well as various publications and brochures from National Committee programs and events, ranging in date from 1971 to 2014.
  - National Committee on U. S. - China Relations: General, 1971-2000 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    David Gergen, Reflections on the New World Order, April 1991 (Conversations in China Series); David M. Lampton, America's China Policy: Developing a Fifth Strategy (Academy of Political Science), 1991; A.. Doak Barnett Memorial Essay Contest on United States - China Relations: Award-Winning Essays, 2000 (2 copies).
  - FA1185:032 - National Committee on U. S. - China Relations: General, 1971; Published Material (Box FA1185:032)
    Removed to RAC Library collection.
    Taiwan and American Policy: The Dilemma in U. S.- China Relations.
  - FA1185:033 - National Committee on U. S. - China Relations: General, 1976; Published Material (Box FA1185:033)
    China: A Resource and Curriculum Guide. Ed. Arlene Posner and Arne J. de Keijzer. 2nd ed., revised.
  - FA1185:034 - National Committee on U. S. - China Relations: General, 1973; Published Material (Box FA1185:034)
    China's Developmental Experience.Ed. Michel Oksenberg. Proceedings of the Academy of Political Science, 31:1. Meetings sponsored by the APS and the NCUSCR at Columbia University, 1972 October 26-28.
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations: Brochures (General), 1973-2012 (Box 13, Folder 112-113)
    Publications and Resources, General Program, Business and Professional Associates, Congressional Trips to the People's Republic of China. Includes "From Ping Pong to the Present: Shaping U. S. - China Relations in the 21st Century. The Mission and Programs of the NCUSCR." Documentary film made in 2012 for the PBS series "The Visionaries."
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations: Brochures (General) (From Ping Pong to the Present), 2012; Digital: DVD-R (1 hour). (Box 13, Folder 113)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    From Ping Pong to the Present: Shaping U. S. - China Relations in the 21st Century. The Mission and Programs of the NCUSCR. Documentary film made for the PBS series "The Visionaries."
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations: Brochures (General) (From Ping Pong to the Present), 2012; DVD-R (1 hour) (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations: Event Programs and Brochures, 1992-2000, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations: Event Programs and Brochures (Cohosted Events for Senior Chinese Leaders), 2008-2013 (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - National Committee on United States - China Relations: Forty at Forty and A Celebration of Anniversaries, 2006, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    Forty at Forth (2 copies); A Celebration of Anniversaries: 45 Years of the National Committee and 40 Years of Jan Berris, May 23, 2011 (brochure).
  - United States and China Relations at a Crossroads, 1993 February (Box 14, Folder 117)
    Policy Paper. Published by the Atlantic Counci of the United States and the NCUSCR. Two copies.
  - Ping Pong Diplomacy, 1972, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    Program Brochure, 1972, and booklet, China - U.S. "Ping Pong Diplomacy" Commemoration, 1997. Booklet in English and Chinese. 2 copies.
  - China Policy Series, 1989-2002 (Box 14, Folder 119-120)
    NCUSCR series of pamphlet publications, nos. 1-10 and 11-18.
  - China Policy Series, 2003-2007 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    NCUSCR series of pamphlet publications, nos. 19-23. Two copies of no. 23.
  - A Sustainable Land Use and Allocation Program for the Ussuri-Wusuli River Watershed and Adjacent Territories (Northeastern China and the Russian Far East), 1996 November; Bound volume (Box 33, Folder 314)
    Cooperative project of the NCUSCR and others. In English, Russian, and Chinese.
- Programs, Projects, and Proposals, 1980-2014; 8
  The Programs, Projects, and Proposals series in RG 3 contains records relating especially to the China Town Hall program and the Scholar Orientation Program, and to surveys the National Committee conducted for the Ford Foundation and the MacArthur Foundation.
  Launched in 2007, the China Town Hall program seeks to foster a national conversation on China and issues pertaining to U. S. – China relations. The annual program features a national webcast address by a prominent speaker, which is paired with local speaker and discussion programs organized at venues around the country. Materials in RG 3 pertain mainly to planning and organization for the 2007 and 2008 programs.
  The Scholar Orientation Program (SOP), which ran from 1980 to 2002, sought to ensure that Chinese scholars and students pursing advanced studies in the U.S. would return to China with a fuller understanding and appreciation of U.S. history, culture, and government. Grouping participants by common interests (such as Law, Economics, or American Studies), the National Committee ran two-week study tours that usually included visits to Williamsburg or Boston, Washington, DC, Philadelphia, and New York. Participants visited historic sites and cultural institutions, attended lectures, and met with officials and professional colleagues; visits also usually included a homestay in the Washington, DC, area with National Committee members and friends. The National Committee organized several SOP trips a year, which it numbered consecutively. The files, which tend to be slim, contain name lists, itineraries, some host-family information, and occasional reports or clippings; later files also include travel and programming information. For Teachers Orientation Programs, which were numbered in sequence with the other SOP delegations, see the Exchanges – General series.
  This segment of the Programs, Projects, and Proposals series also includes records of a survey the National Committee conducted for the Ford Foundation in 2000 on U. S. organizations with programs relating to U.S. – China Relations and Security Issues. The National Committee submitted its internal report to the foundation in January 2003 and updated it in 2005, again at Ford's behest. This second internal report, Survey of Programs on United States – China Relations and Security Issues, submitted in January 2006, formed the basis for the public report of the same title published in the China Policy Series (no. 23) in March 2007. The files include copies of both reports, survey responses, plus a small amount of correspondence. This series also includes one file on the National Committee's Fall 2006 survey for the MacArthur Foundation concerning Chinese Programs on International Relations and Asian Security Issues.
  Finally, this series also contains a set of files labeled "Background Readings," which consists of copies of articles and notes, dated 1972 – 2003, relating especially to religion in China. These readings files probably belonged to Jason Kindopp, a resident scholar at the NCUSCR who was studying unofficial religious groups in China.
  - China Town Hall: Program Brochures, 2007-2014 (Box 12, Folder 95)
  - China Town Hall: Brochure and Drafts, 2007 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 96)
  - China Town Hall: Planning and Press, 2007 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    Also includes Logistics and Finances.
  - China Town Hall: Planning Notebook, 2007 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    Anna Bautista notebook.
  - China Town Hall: Speakers, 2007 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 99)
  - China Town Hall: Congressional Invitations, 2007 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 100)
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Arizona - Hawaii), 2007 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    Honolulu file includes DVD of Town Hall program.
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Arizona - Hawaii) (Honolulu), 2007 May 31; Digital: DVD-R (Box 12, Folder 101)
    China Town Hall, Honolulu, HI, May 31, 2007.
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Illinois - Missouri), 2007 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Nevada -Washington), 2007 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    Tulsa file includes CD of Town Hall interview. DVD of program broadcast by Long Island station added to New York file.
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Nevada -Washington) (Channel 20, Public Access TV, Great Neck, NY, 2007 July 18), 2007 May 31; Digital: DVD. Run time 56:00. (Box 13, Folder 103)
    DVD of China Town Hall, broadcast by Channel 20, Public Access TV, Great Neck, North Shore, Long Island, NY, July 18, 2007.
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Nevada -Washington) (Studio Tulsa interview of Allen Barber), 2007 May 31; Digital: CD-R (Box 13, Folder 103)
    Interview of I. Allen Barber II, China Town Hall, Tulsa, OK, on Studio Tulso, Public Radio Tulsa. Enclosed in Barber to Jan Berris, February 1, 2008.
  - China Town Hall: Webcast Technology and Public Relations, 2007 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - China Town Hall: Follow-Up Report, 2007 May 31 (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - FA1185:030 - China Town Hall: Follow-Up Report, 2007 May 31; Moving Image: BetacamSP tape. (Box FA1185:030)
    China Town Hall, 5-31-07. Master, labeled VT25. 60 minutes.
  - China Town Hall: General Planning, 2008 April 17 (Box 13, Folder 106-107)
  - FA1185: 037 - China Town Hall: General Planning, 2008 April 17; Moving Image: BetacamSP tape (Box FA1185:037)
    China Town Hall, 4.17.08. Master. 60 minutes.
  - China Town Hall: General Planning, 2008 April 17; Digital: DVD+R (Box 13, Folder 106)
    DVD. Reuters label on case: China Town Hall, 4.17.08. Number 655731 added on back of case.
  - China Town Hall: Finances and Follow-Up, 2008 April 17 (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations, 2008 April 17 (Box 13, Folder 109-110)
    Filed alphabetically by name of city or state. Sarasota file includes CD of program.
  - China Town Hall: Local Presentations (Sarasota), 2008 April 17; Digital: CD-R. 80 minutes. (Box 13, Folder 110)
    CD of China Town Hall, Sarasota.
  - Background Readings: Education, 1972-1978 (Box 15, Folder 122-123)
  - Background Readings: Hong Kong Legal System, 1998-2000; Published Material (Box 15, Folder 124)
    Annual reports of the Department of Justice and the Hong Kong Judiciary. Legal System in Hong Kong report retained in file; annual reports noted and discarded.
  - Background Readings: Human Rights, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 125)
  - Background Readings: Social Theory, 1992-1999 (Box 15, Folder 126-127)
  - Background Readings: Social Theory, 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Background Readings: Social Movements, 1996-2002 (Box 16, Folder 129-130)
  - Background Readings: Religion in China: Project Proposals, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - Background Readings: Religion - General, 1993-2003 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    File appears to belong to Jason Kindopp, NCUSCR resident scholar, who was conducting a comparative study of unofficial religious groups in contemporary China.
  - Background Readings: Religion - Christianity and Lightning Cult, 1990s-2002 (Box 16, Folder 133-134)
  - Background Readings: Religion - Revision Notes and Material, 1996-2003 (Box 17, Folder 135)
  - Background Readings: Religion - U. S. - China Christian Issues, 1992-2003 (Box 17, Folder 136-137)
  - Background Readings: Religious Freedom and Political Environment, 1998, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    Includes copy of John L. Holden, Beijing Trip Notes, July 6-13, 2003.
  - Background Readings: Rule of Law and Corruption, circa 1996-2002 (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Background Readings: Civil Society in China, 1998-2002 (Box 17, Folder 140)
  - Background Readings: Media in China, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  - Background Readings: Chinese Language Publications, 2000, undated (Box 17, Folder 142)
    File contains possible conference paper dated December 21-23, 2000; and undated workbook type publication, 200 pages, spiralbound. Subject unknown.
  - Background Readings: Woodpecker, 1996, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 143)
    Serial publication. Woodpecker Bimonthly (1996) and Woodpecker Monthly (2000).
  - Taiwan Conference Background Readings, 2003 August 8-10 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    New Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait: Defining America's Role (Pocantico Center).
  - Scholar Orientation Program: Data, 1989-1992 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    Also includes 1987 note about possible candidate Li Xianglu.
  - Scholar Orientation Program: Ford Foundation Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 147)
    For funding of Women's Issues and Poverty Alleviation scholar orientation programs. Includes SOP data for 1993 and 1996.
  - Scholar Orientation Program: Itineraries, 1991-1992, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 148)
  - Scholar Orientation Program: Journalism Correspondence, 1986-1994 (Box 18, Folder 149)
  - Scholar Orientation Program: Mailing Lists and Information (1997 SOP Info), 1994-1997; Digital: 3.5" floppy disk. (Box 18, Folder 150)
    Disk labeled "1997 SOP information. Mailing-application memos."
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 1), 1980 June 7-14 (Box 18, Folder 151)
    Itineraries and namelists.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 2), 1980 September 7-16 (Box 18, Folder 152)
    English Literature. Namelists and Itinerary.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 3), 1980 December 12-22 (Box 18, Folder 153)
    Agriculture.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 4), 1981 March 18-29 (Box 18, Folder 154)
    Journalists.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 5), 1981 August 12-24 (Box 18, Folder 155)
    English Language and Literature.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 6-7), 1982 March-May (Box 18, Folder 156)
    SOP 6, 1982 March 25-April 5, Mixed; SOP 7, 1982 May 16-27, Foreign Policy.
  - FA1185:005 - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 6-7), 1982 March-May; Still Image: Black and white 3.5 x. 5 snapshot. (Box 18, Folder 156)
    Group photo of SOP 7 Foreign Policy delegation, 1982 May 16-27.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 8-9), 1982 August-September, December (Box 18, Folder 157)
    SOP 8, 1982 August 22- September 2, English Language and Literature; SOP 9, 1982 December 5-19, American History.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 10), 1983 March 15-27 (Box 18, Folder 158)
    Foreign Policy. Includes Evaluations by participants.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 11-12), 1983 June-August (Box 18, Folder 159)
    SOP 11, 1983 June 25 - July 8, Legal Studies; SOP 12, 1983 August 13-24, Journalists.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 13-16), 1984 April-June (Box 18, Folder 160)
    SOP 13, 1984 April 3-14, English Language and Literature; SOP 14, 1984 May 9-22, Law; SOP 15, 1984 May 15-30, Journalists; SOP 16, 1984 June 13-26, Law.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 17-18), 1984 August and October (Box 18, Folder 161)
    SOP 17, 1984 August 10-22, Economists; SOP 18, 1984 October 3-16, American History and International Relations.
  - FA1185:006 - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 17), 1984 August; Still Image: Color 3x5 print. (Box 34, Folder 161)
    Group photo of SOP 17, Economists delegation.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 19-22), 1985 May-July (Box 19, Folder 162)
    SOP 19, 1985 May 17 - June 1, Journalists; SOP 20, 1985 June 5-17, International Law and Economics-Trade; SOP 21, 1985 June 24 - July 6, American Studies; SOP 22, 1985 July 10-22, English Language and Literature.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 23-27), 1986 March-July (Box 19, Folder 163)
    SOP 23, 1986 March 15-27, Education; SOP 24, 1986 May 13-28, Journalism (Parvin Fellows at the University of Hawaii); SOP 25, 1986 June 12-24, Law; SOP 26, 1986 July 2-15, American Studies; SOP 27, 1986 June 25 - July 9, International Relations.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 28-30), 1987 March-June (Box 19, Folder 164)
    SOP 28, 1987 March 18 - April 1, English Language and Literature; SOP 29, 1987 May 11-24, Journalism; SOP 30, 1987 May 28-June 11, Economics and Business Administration
  - FA1185:007 - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 29), 1987 May 11-24; Still Image: 5x7 color snapshots and 8x10 black and white prints. (Box 34, Folder 164)
    SOP 29 visit of Chinese journalists to Richmond Newspapers.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 31-33), 1987 June-July (Box 19, Folder 165)
    SOP 31, 1987 June 7-21, International Relations; SOP 32, 1987 June 18-July 1, American Studies; SOP 33, 1987 July 1-15, Law
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 34-38), 1988 March- July (Box 19, Folder 166)
    SOP 34, 1988 March 16-30, English Language and Literature; SOP 35, 1988 May 5-18, Journalism; SOP 36, 1988 June 9-23, International Relations; SOP 37, 1988 June 16-30, Economics and Business Management; SOP 38, 1988 July 3-17, Law.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 39-43), 1989 March-October (Box 19, Folder 167)
    SOP 39, 1989 March 16-30, International Relations and American Studies; SOP 40, 1989 May 11-24, Journalism; SOP 41, 1989 July 15-29, Economics; SOP 42, 1989 September 7-20, American Studies; SOP 43, 1989 October 12-25, American Studies and English Language and Literature.
  - FA1185:008 - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 39-41), 1989 March-July; Still Images: 1 5x7 black and white print; 6 3x5 - 4x6 color prints. (Box 34, Folder 167)
    Group photos and snapshots of SOP No. 39 - No. 41 delegations, plus one unidentified image.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 45-49), 1990 March-November (Box 19, Folder 168)
    SOP 45, 1990 March 21 - April 4, English Language and Literature; SOP 46, 1990 May 9-23, Journalism; SOP 47. 1990 May 9-23, Economics; SOP 48, 1990 August 9-22, Law; SOP 49, 1990 November 8-21, Education Administration, American Studies and International Relations.
  - FA1185:009 - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 48), 1990 August 9-22; Still Image: 2 4x6 color prints. (Box 34, Folder 168)
    Group photo of delegation, with identifications on back. Two copies.
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 50-54), 1991 April-August (Box 19, Folder 169)
    SOP 50, 1991 April 5-18, Economics; SOP 51, 1991 May 12-25, Journalism; SOP 52, 1991 June 6-19, Education; SOP 53, 1991 July 11-24, American Studies; SOP 54, 1991 August 9-22, International Relations and Law.
  - FA1185:010 - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 53), 1991 July 11-24; Still Image: 2 3x5 color prints. (Box 34, Folder 169)
    Two images of Chen Xiejun with unidentified man (escort William Zarit?).
  - Scholar Orientation Program (No. 55-59), 1992 January-July (Box 19, Folder 170)
    SOP (55), 1992 January 9-22, Orientation Program in International Relations and American Studies for Consular Staff; SOP 56, 1992 April 2-15, Economics; SOP 57, 1992 May 10-22, Journalism; SOP 58, 1992 June 11-24, Law; SOP 59, 1992 July 9-22, English Language and Literature.